&gt；&gt；演讲者1：我对编译时的函数有一个问题
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: I have a question about the function when the compilation is
发生了，其他类的函数在大理石中得到了它的内容，你说了吗？
happening, the function other class gets its contents in the marble did you say?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不确定我在听什么。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm not sure I'm following.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：所以当其他类被编译时-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So when other class is being compiled-
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：有一张地图，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There's a map,
就像一个计划，就像一个路线图，由编译器编出来说，对于
like a plan, like a roadmap, made up by the compiler to say, for
那个蓝色的桶，你需要创建一个叫做教师的标识符。
that blue bucket, you need to create an identifier called teacher.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，这就是编译器输出基本上是一个计划
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, that's what compiler outputs is basically a plan for
那个望远镜。
that scope.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：那么目标部分什么时候发生？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So when does the targeting part happen?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是在运行时，也就是我们现在所处的阶段。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's at run time, which is the stage we're in now.
在运行时，当other Class函数从某个变量中拉出时，
At run time, when that otherClass function is pulled from some variable,
就像是在第13行，并且
like it is on line 13, and
它被执行了，现在我们知道有一个完整的计划来制作这个蓝色的桶。
it's executed, well now we know there's a whole plan to make this blue bucket.
所以让我们先把所有的弹珠做成整个蓝色的桶，然后
So let's go first make the whole blue bucket with all the marbles, and
现在我们在它里面，我们正在运行它。
now we're in it and we're running it.
当我们穿过四号线时，
And when we run across line four,
目标位置有一个叫老师的大理石。
there's a marble called teacher in the target position.
所以我们发现了源和目标的位置
So we discover the source versus target position
在编译时，但是我们直到运行时才使用该信息。
at compile time, but we don't use that information until run time.
这有帮助吗？
Does that help?
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：是的，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yep, thank you.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：所以它本质上创建了一个占位符？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So it creates a place holder essentially?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，基本上把它想成一张藏宝图，对吧。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, basically think of it like a treasure map, right.
有一张地图，有一个计划，就像每个范围的任务清单，
There's a map, there's a plan, it's like a to do list for every scope,
这就是编译器输出的内容，这就是可执行代码。
that's what compiler outputs, that's the executable code.
然后，当它运行的时候，当它真正存在的时候。
And then when it runs is when it all actually comes into existence.
是啊。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：还有一个问题。
Yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: One more question.
当我们输入该函数的范围时，我的意思是如果我们输入
When we enter the scope of that function, I mean if we enter
多次，还有另一个重置值和东西的过程。
multiple times, there's another process that resets the values and things.
你知道我在说什么吗？
How does that work, you know what I'm saying?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：每次执行函数时，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Every time you execute a function,
从头开始重新创建环境。
the environment is recreated from scratch.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：好的，那么这实际上是什么，它在编译器中是什么样子的？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Okay, so what does that actually, is it like in the compiler?
我不知道。
I don't know.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以请记住，编译器只为bucket制定计划，它说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So remember, the compiler only makes a plan for the bucket, it says,
嘿，无论何时你需要一个绿色的水桶，这就是绿色水桶应该看起来的样子
hey whenever you need a green bucket, this is what the green bucket ought to look
就像，这是它的内容应该是的，但它实际上还不存在。
like, and this is what it's contents ought to be, but it doesn't actually exist yet.
然后每次执行绿色桶时，该计划都会影响到内存中。
And then every time you execute the green bucket, that plan is effected into memory.
然后当绿色的水桶完成了这个计划，所有的东西都消失了，而且
And then when the green bucket finishes that plan, all that stuff goes away, and
然后下次运行它时，它会再次从计划中创建它，好吧。
then the next time you run it, it creates it from the plan again, okay.
所以编译器输出实际上不是保留的内存，它是计划
So the compiler output is not actually reserved memory, it's the plan for
如何保留记忆和制作弹珠等等。
how to reserve memory and make marbles and all that.